<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HunieBee</string>
    <string name="title_activity_detail">Detail</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="aiko_description">
        Aiko is slender with curvy hips and fairly large breasts. She has gray eyes that match the
        color of her hair, which extends to her shoulders. Her hair also consists of a white
        hairclip. In her usual outfit, she wears a loose, black neck tie with a green jacket and a
        white crop top. She wears glasses with a circular frame, wears white shorts, and wears red
        high heels.
    </string>
    <string name="aiko_personality">
        Aiko is a university professor but doesn\'t much care for the position. She is apathetic
        towards and detached from academia and often feels overwhelmed and under qualified. She\'s
        uncertain of what she really wants to do with her life and is really just coasting through
        her days; often miserable or borderline depressed. Despite this, she’s a very humorous
        person and uses jokes and laughter as a means to temporarily escape or mask her general
        misery.
    </string>
    <string name="aiko_history">
        Aiko went to College for 6 years and is now a substitute teacher who found herself in a
        long term teaching gig at the local college because of the absence of one of the school’s
        prominent math and science professors. It’s a responsibility she reluctantly accepts as
        living up to the legacy of her predecessor proves difficult. She often has Tiffany and Audrey
        in her classes. Despite her knowledge of odds and statistics, Aiko has developed a gambling
        addiction and can be found at the casino almost every night.
    </string>

    <string name="audrey_description">
        Audrey has a slim build along with small breasts. She has red eyes that match her faded red
        hair which extends to her midback and has a black rose/ribbon with a white veil on top of her
        hair. In her default outfit, she wears a red Lolita type dress with her shirt being red plaid
        with white squares, and a red and black patterned ribbon attached to the front of it. She wears
        a red collar with a black tie. She wears a red skirt with a red-and-white plaid horizontal ruffle
        in the middle, the two other ruffles being red. She has a black bow on her back and wears white high
        heels that also have black bows attached to them. There\'s also a red ribbon tied around her left ankle.
    </string>
    <string name="audrey_personality">
        Audrey is loud, self centered and an all around stuck up bitch. She has extremely high energy and believes life is a party that\'s meant to be enjoyed. As a result, she all too often indulges in reckless behaviors like smoking, drinking, recreational drug use, casual sex, ignoring her education, rejecting authority and generally doing whatever she feels like. Audrey has no real sense of loyalty or commitment and is only looking to have as much fun as possible.
    </string>
    <string name="audrey_history">
        Audrey is a college student studying cosmetology. Unlike her friend and classmate Tiffany, she doesn’t care for the academic setting and does not take her school work very seriously. She can often be found skipping class and hanging out at the Mall. Audrey is a self described party girl. She admires Jessie’s carefree lifestyle and tries to emulate her. She loves to go dancing and drags her friends to the local nightclub several times a week. Though the extent of the problem is unclear, Tiffany and Nikki suspect Audrey of having drug abuse issues.
    </string>


    <string name="beli_description">Beli is tall with very long black hair that extends to her groin. Her eyes are fuchsia and her skin color/background suggests that she is Indian. In her default outfit, she wears a short purple top that shows the entirety of her midriff along with sheer, loose pants that also show her underwear or a pair of shorts underneath. This is accented with her gold bangle, necklace, headpiece, and shoes. She, like most women in the game, has large breasts and a thin build.</string>
    <string name="beli_personality">Though she does not consider herself a religious person, Beli is in tune with her spiritual side. She tries to maintain a calm, relaxed, and subdued state of mind. She’s very trusting and submissive; making her a pushover. She’s an approval-seeker and feels the need for people to like her. Beli fears inadequacy and is always afraid that she’s doing something wrong. She has a poor body image and is upset about her eating habits, but seems too weak to change.</string>
    <string name="beli_history">Beli instructs meditative yoga classes at the local gym. Though she does not consider herself a religious person she is very in-tune with her spiritual side. As somebody who grew up around Hindu influences she tends to stray away from things like drinking and partying, opting instead to spend her time doing more self-developmental exercises like meditation and nature walks. She loves to be outdoors and can often be found relaxing at the park. Beli tries hard to stick to a healthy vegan diet but has a crippling weakness for fried foods and sweets. She has developed strong friendships with some of the girls who take her class including Kyanna, Lola, and perhaps most unlikely of all, Jessie.</string>

    <string name="jessie_description">Jessie has a curved in build with relatively large breasts. She has blue eyes that match her blonde hair. Her hair extends to her shoulders. Her default outfit consists of a leopard print top that seems to be accessorized with a belt at the waist, navy blue jean shorts, and dark brown ankle-high boots.</string>
    <string name="jessie_personality">After having her daughter Tiffany at the young age of 16, Jessie got into adult film to support her and her daughter but quickly fell in love with the money and attention. Because she wasn\'t able to experience the carefree youthfulness of her late teens and twenties, she never outgrew her wild side and tends to overcompensate for those lost years. Jessie is carefree, selfish, and manipulative. She has no shame when it comes to her body or her sexuality.</string>
    <string name="jessie_history">No known history.</string>

    <string name="kyanna_description">Kyanna bears an immaculate and curvaceous build with large breasts. She has violet eyes to match her black hair that extends to her hips, also wearing a white headband on top of her hair. In her usual attire, she has gold, heart-shaped earrings in between the front and back layers of her hair. She wears a pale blue tank top with darker blue horizontal stripes, and wears short, navy blue pants.</string>
    <string name="kyanna_personality">Kyanna is a hair stylist at the salon in the mall. She\'s obsessed with beauty and body image, spending most of her free time at the gym. She\'s loyal and protective of her friends, but get on her bad side and things change quickly. Growing up with only brothers, she\'s a bit of a tomboy. Kyanna is the mother to a one year old baby. She got knocked up a year ago but the father is not in either of their lives. As such, she values honesty, responsibility and stability.</string>
    <string name="kyanna_history">Kyanna is a hairdresser and stylist at the beauty shop in the mall, but she dreams of becoming a famous actress, singer and dancer. As a result, she is obsessed with beauty and body image. She spends most of her free time working out at the gym and doesn\'t miss one of Beli’s yoga classes. While she can be a bit vain at times, she is loyal to a fault and very protective of her family and friends. She has a one year old son named Philip, though it\'s unclear what happened to the father of Kyanna\'s child, whether he left when she was pregnant, or if he died, Kyu only said he wasn\'t in their lives and that Kyanna never talked much about him and only mentioned her son Phillip a few times during dates, and it\'s unclear whether her relationship with her son\'s father was serious or not. But she did get upset when Audrey insulted her saying "Why don\'t you go, and get knocked up again!?" and called her a whore. She dropped out of high school sometime in her life. While fans speculated she left high school because she got pregnant, that isn\'t the case as she is twenty-one and her son is a year old and she met her son\'s father at twenty, so she left high school for unknown reasons.</string>

    <string name="kyu_description">Kyu has a slender physique, with curved hips and fairy small breasts. She has green eyes that contrast her pink, pig-tailed hair which extends to just above her shoulders. Her hair also has two decorative silver antennae. Her default outfit consists of a pink and white baby-doll lingerie with light-pink panties that have a purple butterfly shape attached to the front of them. She wears a white collared necklace with a pink choker top that has a red heart shape on the front of it. She has large, butterfly-like, translucent fairy wings that are patterned in pink, wears light pink stockings which cover the lower parts of her thighs, and wears purple ballerina shoes.</string>
    <string name="kyu_personality">Though she is very old by human standards she is quite young in fairy years. Sexuality is a way of life for Kyu and her people. Love fairies are almost vampiric in their need for humans to sustain life; but it isn\'t blood that they suck. As a bisexual, Kyu is often attracted to the same girls you are and isn\'t afraid to tell you what she\'d like to do to them. She even collects female underwear because, well, she just really likes the smell."</string>
    <string name="kyu_history">Kyu is a magic love fairy hailing from the mythical Sky Garden. As a humble servant to the great Love Goddess, it\'s Kyu\'s responsibility to spread love throughout the human world. She will be assigned to your case and after helping you get started on your quest she will hang around to offer advice.</string>

    <string name="lola_description">Lola has an average build with rather large breasts. She has dark gray eyes that match her curly, medium brown hair that merely extends to her neck. In her default outfit, she wears a pale blue flight attendant uniform that completely covers her hips. She wears a white scarf, shoes, fencenet stockings that cover some part of her thighs, and gloves that extend no longer than her palms.</string>
    <string name="lola_personality">Being a flight attendant, Lola tends not to be in one place for too long. She’s a confident and independent woman with entrepreneurial ambitions. Though she has goals that she is working toward, she’s quite happy with her life and has an aura of contentedness around her. She\'s generally very nice and loves to laugh; but has a bitchy side when angered. Lola aspires to be a great Tennis player and can often be found practicing at the courts near the Park.</string>
    <string name="lola_history">No known history.</string>

    <string name="nikki_description">Nikki has a slim physique. Her blue eyes match the color of her hair that only extend to her shoulders, and wears glasses with a frame large enough to cover her eyelashes. In her usual attire, she wears an oversized sweater that is slanted to show her bra strap. She also wears white shorts that are patterned in black. She wears black shoes with white patterns and grey shoelaces.</string>
    <string name="nikki_personality">Nikki despises her job as a barista at the Cafe. She doesn\'t particularly like or trust people and certainly doesn\'t go out of her way to accommodate them or make them feel welcome. She is almost always cold and distant to new people she meets, but she\'ll warm up to those who she feels understand her. Nikki spends her free time at home playing video games, browsing the web, reading comics, updating her blog and getting involved in conspiracy theories.</string>
    <string name="nikki_history">Nikki works at the Cafe as a Barista. She would go to university with her friends Tiffany and Audrey if she didn’t believe it was a waste of her time. As an autodidact, she’s really good at teaching herself anything she needs to know. She spends a lot of time at her computer browsing the internet, reading web comics, updating her blog and getting involved in conspiracy theory groups just for fun. In addition to being a talented artist, Nikki is an avid gamer and sinks a large chunk of her paycheck into arcade machines every week.</string>

    <string name="tiffany_description">Tiffany is very slender with medium sized breasts and long, blonde hair that extends to her hips. Her facial expression is typically happy and she has blue eyes. She tends to have her right hand behind her head (with the exception of her photos) and seems to be healthy. Her default outfit is typical schoolgirl attire: including a plaid skirt, matching button-up top, thigh-high stockings, black shoes, and pigtails tied with red ribbon.</string>
    <string name="tiffany_personality">Tiffany is a university student who takes her academic work seriously and it shows on her marks. In addition to being the head cheerleader for her school, she\'s involved in several other extracurricular activities. She’s kind to others and cares about the people close to her. She maintains a healthy work/life balance and knows how to have fun. Tiffany does not get along with her mother Jessie and tries to stay away from her mother\'s lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="tiffany_history">Tiffany is a college student who is studying to become a nurse. She takes her academic work very seriously and it shows on her marks. In addition to being the head cheerleader for her school, she is involved in several extracurricular and student life activities. Though she rarely has any, she likes to spend free time at the beach or relaxing in her dorm with her friends Audrey and Nikki. Tiffany does not get along with her mother Jessie and makes great strides to stay away from her mother and her lifestyle.</string>

    <string name="celeste_description">Celeste has dark blue skin, dark blue horns, red eyes, and grey hair that is shoulder length with bangs. Her body is more curvaceous than most of the other girls and she has very large breasts. Her spacesuit appears to be either leather or latex and has a hole on the chest to reveal cleavage. Her suit matches with her colors scheme of blue and white.</string>
    <string name="celeste_personality">Celeste is an intergalactic bounty hunter who hunts various alien fugitives across the known universe. She prefers to be out at night, as her species is nocturnal, and her alien appearance is less noticeable to anyone she might encounter. This may also explain why she can be commonly found in the night club. Celeste is intelligent and knowledgeable about the universe, and will commonly test the player\'s knowledge of space through questions about various celestial bodies in the Solar System and beyond, as well as other general knowledge about the cosmos. Celeste is kind and friendly to the player, and speaks in a somewhat stiff and mechanical, but grammatically correct and fluent manner, though her knowledge of idioms and metaphors can be somewhat lacking. This peculiar way of speaking can most likely be ascribed to her unfamiliarity with Earth languages and the planet\'s inhabitants, though how she came to speak the language of the player is unknown; however, this can be dismissed as a necessity to the plot.</string>
    <string name="celeste_history">No known history.</string>

    <string name="momo_description">In Momo\'s default appearance, she has short, red hair that extends no further than her shoulders and bangs along with golden eyes and a narrow pupil which represents that of a cat\'s eye. Momo is also pale and has long, thick legs with a curved waist. Momo has a black collar with a bell on her neck and wears a short, navy blue kimono with a design of a white streak pattern across the top and white flowers and also has a little bow on her tail that has the same pattern as the kimono. On her feet, she wears white socks with brown sandals to match with the outfit. Like a cat, Momo has black cat ears with white, fluffy fur and a black tail with white fur at the end on her backside. Like other characters, Momo has various outfits and hairstyles that are unlockable throughout the game.</string>
    <string name="momo_personality">She is very sweet, innocent and adorable; with a naive child-like mentality about most things. She loves to run around outside and play in the sun but tends to come back inside at night. Momo lives to make her master happy. Once you discover how to unlock her and become her new master, she will become very attached to you.</string>
    <string name="momo_history">Momo is a stray cat girl that is in desperate need of a master. Momo\'s origins are unknown.</string>

    <string name="venus_description">The Goddess wears a red and white robe with pure golden bracelets and laces, reminiscent of Greco-Roman apparel. Her hair is mint green and falls to her thighs; it is accessorized with a laurel wreath made of gold. Venus is buxom and sports a very curvaceous hourglass figure, with large breasts and wide hips.</string>
    <string name="venus_personality">As the Goddess of Love, Venus is in charge of all the love fairies. Her goal is to assist humans in finding their true love, or at least help them gain confidence in the romance department. Venus is somewhat haughty, being a goddess, and greets and speaks with the player in a regal manner becoming of her status. While not exactly friendly, she does not act demeaning or hostile towards the player, and treats them with an appropriate level of respect. As the player dates her, she makes it clear that she is testing them at every step. When she asks the player questions, they will most often pertain to specific details about the girls they have dated. Dates will also be more difficult, as the player must obtain an high score, making high-scoring combos and trait upgrades more crucial than ever for the player to be successful on dates.</string>
    <string name="venus_history">Aphrodite lived on Mount Olympus with the other supreme deities and was married to the homely craftsman-god, Hephaestus. She was said to have been born from the foam of the sea. Aphrodite involved herself on several noteworthy occasions with the affairs of mortal heroes. When Jason asked permission of the king of Colchis to remove the Golden Fleece from the grove in which it hung, the king was clearly unwilling. So the goddess Hera, who sponsored Jason\'s quest, asked Aphrodite to intervene. The love goddess made the king\'s daughter Medea fall in love with Jason, and Medea proved instrumental in Jason\'s success. </string>

    <string name="credits">App developed by xkdawg {Kevin D\'Souza}.\nOriginal game and most artwork created by Huniepot. All rights belong to the original creator. </string>
    <string name="image_settings_desc">Set the probability of how often each image should be shown.</string>
</resources>
